profitgainer.com 2012-08-04

# Profit Gainer

We may collect personal information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.  
Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, username, email address.

We will collect personal information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.  
The information you provide to us on the Registration page such as name, username and email address is maintained in private files on our web server.

This information will never share to anyone without your authorization. Your information will be private and will not be released to the third parties.   
We implement proper data collection, storage and security measurement to protect against unauthorized access, modification, of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

You can update or correct your contact information at any time by contacting Profit Gainer at profitgainercom@yahoo.com. We reserve the right to change or amend this Privacy Statement as needed to address changes in business practices or in privacy laws or regulations. Changes or amendments will be noted on this page on our web site.  
If you would like to send us a request as point out above or you have any inquiries or concern about Privacy Policy, Please don't be hesitate to contact us at profitgainercom@yahoo.com
